Redemption.
Forsaken is a western, action, drama film directed by Jon Cassar.
John Henry returns to his hometown in hopes of repairing his relationship with
his estranged father, but a local gang is terrorizing the town.
John Henry is the only one who can stop them, however he has abandoned
both his gun and reputation as a fearless quick-draw killer.
Mary-Alice Watson, played by Demi Moore.
John Henry Clayton, played by Kiefer Sutherland.
Rev. Clayton, played by Donald Sutherland.
James McCurdy, played by Brian Cox.
Emily Chadwick, played by Siobhan Williams.
Dave Turner, played by Michael Wincott.
Forsaken is a 2015 revisionist Western film directed by Jon
Cassar, from a screenplay by Brad Mirman.
The film stars Kiefer Sutherland, Donald Sutherland, Brian Cox,
Michael Wincott, Aaron Poole and Demi Moore.
The film had its world premiere at the Toronto
International Film Festival on September 16, 2015.
The film was released on February 19, 2016.
One of the executive producers on the film was Doug Falconer.
The film explores themes of small town, gunslinger, saloon, gang, shootout.
The tone is emotional.